First of all, this strap is already worn on the model, but it has a slightly stretched shape when worn, so we will select the strap version and open it, and switch the strap type to a harder type, and then simulate it.
After simulation, you can see that the strap is not deformed, and it is worn on the model.
Now we turn to the back of the model to make the ring of the strap.
First, we use the shape tool to make a ring plate and enter a suitable size.
Then we sew the plate to the position of the back piece.
After sewing, we switch to the tool, add to the side at the 3D window, and quickly arrange the board in a position near the model.
Then we can use the positioning ball to move the board.
Then we use the positioning ball to move the board.
Then we need to add an inner line in the middle of this panel to fold it, and before we fold it, we will harden this panel.
After hardening, we can model it and let it level. After leveling, use the folding arrangement tool to make a fold for it.
Change the fold angle to 0, and then sew it. Remember to change the model type to TURN.
After modeling, because this panel is very small, we will reduce its particle diameter, and the thickness of the gap will also be reduced.
Remove its hardening.
We want this panel to be a little bit rounder, so we change the inner line angle to 180 degrees.
If you want it to be more round, you can make the folding strength bigger, and make it stronger to maintain the 180 degree angle.
Okay, now we are done.
Now we need to make a sewing fixation on this part of the strap.
Remove the previous sewing line first.
After removing it, we put the other side of the panel on the other side.
Give it a colon.
Colon symmetrical panel.
Then freeze the back of our back.
The strap panel can also be frozen.
After modeling, we will activate the two straps.
After activating, we need to sew it on the panel of the belt we made.
We need to sew it on the panel of the belt we made.
Then sew it on the panel of the belt we made.
When sewing, if you can't find the right position, you can see it in 3D.
Then slightly adjust its position.
And the example of these two panels can also be reduced to 3.
Okay, so he sewed it on the board of our two belts
After sewing, in order to make the shape of these two boards
It's not easy to transform, so I'm going to add a sticky layer
In the middle, we still need a belt of a belt to come over
So we have to continue to create a new board
Then we need to measure the length of this new board
Then we use our measuring tool
One-click start, double-click end to measure the length of this section
You can see that this length is now more than 127
Then we create a 130mm board
What about this height?
Because there is no measurement just now, let's measure it again
Use our editing board tool
Look at the width of our belt
It's 7.9
Then we can create a new board
This is a board with a height of 8
After the installation is done, we are in the 3D window
Make arrangements for this board
Arrange it quickly to the back of our model
You can see that there is an arrow tool on our positioning ball
After we click on this tool
The board will move with your mouse to your designated position
Then we use the positioning ball to adjust it
The position of the position
Then we make an example of it
A modification of the building
And add our tape
Then sew
When sewing, we can take a look at the corresponding relationship between 3D and 2D
Don't sew it wrongly!
Like this, I sewed it the other way around
Then I can switch the direction of the sewing line with the ice sewing line tool
That's it
Move it to the middle
I also made this board left and right
Use the plus point division tool
To add two straight points in the middle of our board
Then switch the tool to the adjustment board tool
Select this board and right click
Set to left and right symmetry
Then select this board
In this way, the sewing line is automatically added
Click on the simulation
In this way, our first method of wearing a ring is almost complete
This method is a more stable one
It's actually a fake wear
It's not a real wear
But sew it on this board
So we want to remove the effect of this sewing line
We can use the editor sewing line tool
Select this set of sewing lines
Then adjust the strength of the sewing line in the attribute editor to 0
So you can't see the trace of such a sewing line
And we want to give this board a more
And we will adjust the sewing line to the middle position
This will be more realistic
Because it is fixed from above
Then we can add another thickness of the sewing line
The thickness of the sewing line must be in the opening of our
A thick texture surface
So we can see it
So we adjust it to the thick texture surface to check
In this way, we look like we are passing through
Such a structure
Of course, the middle rope is a little long
In the process of making
Can shorten it a little more
Maybe it will be more realistic
After a little shorter
Then I won't do it here
Now let's talk about the second way of making
That is our real wear
If the real wear
We first delete this fixed sewing line
Then hide this board
Shift plus Q is to hide three boards
After selecting that board
Shift plus Q
You can hide this board separately
Then sew these two boards together
In 3D
We can also sew
After sewing
We shift plus W to show all our boards
Then adjust the position of our board
Let it be in the middle of our ring
To sew
If we say we simulate it directly
There will be some problems
Let's Ctrl Z back
Let's adjust this position again
This side is also
Let's adjust it to the middle
Keep hiding this board
The position between them
Can be pulled closer
Shift plus W to show all the boards
Adjust it
Then freeze the back of the big body
Remove the middle of the board
I will remove it
Make it easier to stretch
When it is like this
It has a deformation
Will be more stable
You can see it now
It's already
Really through
Then
We will remove the big body
This freeze
Can be seen
Now it is a real one
The structure of the ring
Now
We can see
If I say
Add to it
After we simulate
It will still be
Through
So this sticky
To the
One of the effects of simulation
It can be observed from this case
Can be observed
Now I'm going to this board
To switch
Other sticky types
For example, I switched to a
The first
Or the second
This kind of softer sticky
It can be stable
Stay in our ring
Finally
We need to give it this place
Make an optimization
First of all
The effect of our sewing line
Give it to him first
Use our edge sewing line tool
Remove its hair line intensity
Then
At the end of this place
We are going to add a butterfly knot
Butterfly knot
In our
Drawing file
There is a
A
You can simulate it after you wear it, and then bring it over to it in a simulated state.
Then in order to fix its position, we can use our sewing needle tool.
Click on one of our butterfly-shaped panels, and then click on the inner-layer panel to fix it.
Then use this tool to adjust the sewing, to edit the sewing, to edit its position.
After adjustment, we simulate it.
In this way, you can make such a butterfly knot effect.
Switch to our dense pattern surface.
Finally, the effect of hanging a belt and wearing a belt is completed.